const questions: Array<QuestionType> = [
  {
    question: 'ἦρα',
    answers: ['ik tilde op', 'ik nam weg'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἔσπειρα',
    answers: ['ik zaaide'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἤγειρα',
    answers: ['ik wekte op'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἀπέκτεινα',
    answers: ['ik doodde'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἀπέστειλα',
    answers: ['ik zond'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἤγγειλα',
    answers: ['ik verkondigde', 'ik kondigde aan'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'απἤγγειλα',
    answers: ['ik kondigde af'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'παρἤγγειλα',
    answers: ['ik beval'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἔμεινα',
    answers: ['ik bleef'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἔκρινα',
    answers: ['ik oordeelde'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  }
]
const lesson26Aorist2: LessonType = {
  id: 'lesson26-aorist2',
  name: 'Les 26 – Aorist II',
  type: 'woordenschat',
  active: false,
  questions
}
export default lesson26Aorist2
